<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TheGeekBlog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TheGeekBlog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 14:45:38 +0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Steps Towards Success in Your Business</title>
      <link>/posts/7-steps-towards-success-in-your-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 14:45:38 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/7-steps-towards-success-in-your-business/</guid>
      <description>So, you’ve had a eureka moment and the USP for your (imagined or otherwise) product will conduct billions of pounds in revenue overnight… right? Often, people jump into business too quickly without knowing how to survive in the tough early years.
However fantastic your product or service is, you need a way to make people aware of it, and a way to produce enough of it to keep up with demand, and often this is before you have been paid for anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disturbing Trends That Impact Workplace and Worker Morale</title>
      <link>/posts/disturbing-trends-that-impact-workplace-and-worker-morale/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 14:42:28 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/disturbing-trends-that-impact-workplace-and-worker-morale/</guid>
      <description>In this callously competitive epoch where dynamic business trends are constantly permeating the ecosystem of businesses, workplaces and subsequently the worker’s morale is affected the most. Recognition, appreciation, sense of camaraderie are in tandem with fair compensation and flexibility. These are the ubiquitous wants of most workers, irrespective of the generation they belong to.
Also, tumultuous changes over the last few decades and the recent pandemonium caused by COVID 19 have impacted the career path and priorities of every generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Is Better Than Another Programming Language</title>
      <link>/posts/python-is-better-than-another-programming-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 14:39:40 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/python-is-better-than-another-programming-language/</guid>
      <description>As the IT sector has been evolving, there has been a growth of different programming languages C, Java, Python, PHP, Ruby, and more. A career as a software engineer or developer should be made carefully by choosing the right technology to study. Recent market research suggests that IT companies are choosing Python a lot more than other frameworks and languages fo their organizational growth.
Python has also been ranked as the top programming language of 2019 and the upcoming languages of 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invest in Cryptocurrencies Is Now</title>
      <link>/posts/invest-in-cryptocurrencies-is-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 14:32:50 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/invest-in-cryptocurrencies-is-now/</guid>
      <description>Because of the internet, transacting with digital currency is now possible. Do we all remember how it felt to interact through social media a decade ago? Cryptocurrency is in this stage now and is taking its position in the global economy. Actually, experts are optimistic that it will shape the future economy.
The evolution of crypto since it was born compels people to believe that this is a lucrative investment. When you look at the curve, there has been consistent growth and stability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Proven Strategies to Boost Visitors to Your Website</title>
      <link>/posts/5-proven-strategies-to-boost-visitors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 14:28:05 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/5-proven-strategies-to-boost-visitors/</guid>
      <description>I’ve successfully built and marketed my personal training services using only my website and Google.
The proven strategies I share with you below will boost visitors to your website and help you get more traction in the Google search results.
And best of all, they’re 100% free to do yourself. No paid ads required. #1 Harness Video Content
People’s attention span is limited. A picture might be worth a thousand words, so a video could be worth millions!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence: Back to Basics</title>
      <link>/posts/machine-learning-and-artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 13:59:05 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/machine-learning-and-artificial-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>Both Machine learning and artificial intelligence are common terms used in the field of computer science. However, there are some differences between the two. In this article, we are going to talk about the differences that set the two fields apart. The differences will help you get a better understanding of the two fields. Read on to find out more.
Overview
As the name suggests, the term Artificial Intelligence is a combo of two words: Intelligence and Artificial.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>